<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-02-09T21:38:47-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">Woodmansee Wanderlust</title><subtitle>Depictions and descriptions of our travels</subtitle><author><name>Zack Woodmansee</name><email></email><uri>https://github.com/woodmanzee</uri></author><entry><title type="html">Dallas to Austin</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Dallas-to-Austin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dallas to Austin" /><published>2017-02-08T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-02-08T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Dallas%20to%20Austin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Dallas-to-Austin/">&lt;p&gt;Saying goodbye to friends is always hard, but I had better get used to it because we will have to do it again and again this trip. Before we left the Dallas area, we stopped by Zack’s cousin’s place to catch up with them (I would have posted a picture of us all together but we totally forgot to take one…).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On our way to Austin we stopped in a town called West. We had heard that they had yummy kolaches that we needed to try. Up until this point I had never even heard of them, but I quickly learned that they are pastries with a filling in the center. I got pumpkin with cream cheese and Zack got strawberry with cream cheese. They were delicious and now I’m a fan!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Commentary by Z: I posted a little blurb on imgur (social image hosting site) asking people for any food or attraction suggestions in the towns we were visiting, and multiple people told us to stop for these kolaches! Turned out to be worth it imo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/kpvlqPSh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kolaches Z&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/6Bt5ECPh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kolaches H&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/7edtG5Mh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kolaches storefront&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once we left West were only went another 20ish min down the road to…drum roll please!! WACO!  I have been so excited for this leg of the trip because I have wanted to go to Magnolia Market for a while now. What’s so cool about Waco? Well if you aren’t familiar with Fixer Upper on HGTV, you should just check it out. A husband and wife (Chip and Joanna) remodel homes. They can transform any home into someone’s dream home, all they need is to break down a few walls, add a little shiplap and paint and bam! They have a beautiful home for the family moving in. The popularity of the show has helped transform the town into a popular tourist destination. The couple opened Magnolia Market which has 3 buildings around a little grassy square. One offers home decor, another has gardening supplies, and the the last is a bakery. They have turned the square into a place to relax, grab a bite to eat at one of the food trucks, or shop and get some goodies. I love Joanna’s taste in decorating so it was fun to go into a store and see her style. I loved everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/FbVCOhCh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Magnolia Market and H&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/PKfhCZKh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Magnolia Market and swings&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/AW3XUd2h.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Magnolia Market and swings&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was also told to check out the Findery just a block or two down the road. It’s another home decor/clothing store. Their style is similar to Magnolia Market but is slightly cheaper. So if you are ever in the area, I say you should check out both because you may find what you are looking for between the two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/jBmIlTLh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Findery&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For lunch, we heard that we needed to check out Vitek’s bbq so that’s exactly what we did. The place was just off the freeway and like 5 min from Magnolia Market. It did not disappoint. They have Texas BBQ which in my opinion was fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Commentary by Z: this was like my dream lunch - they had a bbq version of taco salad. Comes with fritos on the bottom topped with pulled pork, sausage, baked beans, cheese, onions, and peppers. Was AMAZING.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/sQQmFbsh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Vitek's&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After lunch we weren’t quite ready to leave Waco. We had to see the Dr. Pepper Museum. Did you know that Dr. Pepper was founded in Waco?? I didn’t until someone online told us we should go. The museum was a little run down, but it was still really cool to read about the history of Dr. Pepper. Zack is a Dr Pepper lover and when I first met him I hated it. Over time whenever we were out at dinner and he would order it I would ask to take a sip of it. At first it was gross, but for whatever reason I kept taking one sip at a time and over the course of our marriage I grew to love it. Desensitized maybe? YES, regardless I have been converted. Anyway, back to the museum, while parts of it were a little random (like the wild west exhibit?), they had restored sections on the building where the first Dr Pepper made it’s debut over 100 years ago and being only $10 to get in, to me it was worth it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/LAXlJU0h.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;DrPepperfrontdoor&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/v6CE0hZh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;DrPeppersignZ&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/csQSVqmh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;DrPeppermuseum&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Commentary by Z: There’s something about opening an ice cold Dr. Pepper in a glass bottle in the original Dr. Pepper bottling plant that you can’t get anywhere else&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We spent over 3 hours in Waco, which I was a little surprised by that simply because it was supposed to be a quick stop before heading to my sister’s house, but Waco has more to offer than meets the eye and sometimes a quick stop is not enough!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4th leg of the journey: 10 hours. 253 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/maps/austin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;austin map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Zack Woodmansee</name><uri>https://github.com/woodmanzee</uri></author><category term="Travel" /><category term="Dallas" /><category term="Waco" /><category term="Dr" /><category term="Pepper" /><category term="Texas" /><category term="Wanderlust" /><summary type="html">Saying goodbye to friends is always hard, but I had better get used to it because we will have to do it again and again this trip. Before we left the Dallas area, we stopped by Zack’s cousin’s place to catch up with them (I would have posted a picture of us all together but we totally forgot to take one…).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dallas</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Dallas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dallas" /><published>2017-02-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-02-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Dallas</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Dallas/">&lt;p&gt;Because we went into the city last night, we didn’t go back to the heart of Dallas today. Zack had a bunch of work to do so we stayed in the house most of the morning. We have been staying with some friends at their in-laws’ place. The in-laws have a beautiful ranch and were nice enough to let us all crash at their place for the last two nights. I have definitely had the full Texas experience…or the Texas experience that comes to my mind. The ranch has a few cows (longhorns), horses, and two cute dogs. It’s a dream come true for me because I love all of those things! It really is a beautiful place and I can see the appeal of country living. There’s plenty of wide open space to roam and explore. It is also quiet and peaceful, which is nice after navigating through Dallas rush hour traffic yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Commentary by Z: Pretty sure 75% of the Dallas area is covered by freeways. I’ve never had to take so many on/off ramps and exchanges in a 20 minute drive in my entire life. Didn’t help that half of those roads were under construction!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During our lunch break we went on a run. We just ran to the end of the street and back..sooo two miles. Along the road there were a few houses here and there that sit on 20 plus acres. Horses, cattle, donkeys, and even llamas graze the pastures. It totally lived up to my idea of country living in Texas. It’s easy to get lost in thought out here while enjoying the animal friends that want to greet me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/hdiov3ph.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cattle&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/hlIaUcIh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Zack tying shoe&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/g5gB9Sfh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hannah Running&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Commentary by Z: After growing up in California with lots of hills and then spending the past 10 years in Utah with the mountains, it’s weird to be somewhere with open sky from horizon to horizon. Really makes it feel like there’s a ton more space, just because you can see all of it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight was one to remember though. The Schindlers were great and took us on a buggy ride! They hitched up the horses to the buggy and everyone hopped in. It was dark outside, but that added to the dreaminess of it. The air was crisp and a little breezy when riding with the wind, but I loved it so much. There is something majestic to me when I watch horses. The two pulling the carriage were beautiful, powerful animals. They made it look easy when pulling the carriage and 5 people!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/R4mncohh.jpg?1&quot; alt=&quot;Horses&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/erh4sQSh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;carriage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/LH7nMyOh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;carriage with friends&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because it was dark outside they were a little more skittish than they normally would be. If a car drove by or something came into view that they were unfamiliar with, they would get nervous and try to pick up the pace, but I thought it just made the adventure all the more exciting. We didn’t just take a slow ride through the night, the pace was brisk and always on the verge of turning into a canter. We took a winding 6 mile journey into the night and it went by way too fast for me. The horses were incredible and I was blown away to learn how one even goes about training such creatures. It takes time and a lot of patience. I’ve got plenty of time right now, but patience I think I might lack. I’m just so glad I got to experience something like this during my time on the Ranch. I loved every second of it! So THANK YOU Schindler family!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/C8Dpzqph.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lex, Steph and us&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the carriage ride we went out to dinner at a place called Babe’s Chicken. They have two items on the menu. Country Fried Steak or Fried Chicken. Once you pick between the two they bring out all you can eat sides and sooo much chicken or steak. I barely made a dent in my food but I ate so much! Too much really. Now I feel sick and need to recover before I eat again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Commentary by Z: best part was the corn and biscuits. Pretty sure all the nutritional value of corn was thrown out the window, nothing healthy tastes as good as that corn did. Plus there’s just something about hot buttery biscuits that satisfy a hunger you never knew you had until they’re in front of you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we headed home we were introduced to Buc-ee’s. If you have never heard of it (like me) it’s… a gas station. But not just any gas station. It was the biggest gas station I have ever seen. There were at least a 100 pumps and the store was almost the size of Walmart. We walked inside and they have food, candy, home decor?? and so many other things. It was overwhelming really. The options were endless. If I wanted jerky or anything for that matter they tons of options/flavors to choose from. Who knew a gas station could be so exciting? Not me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/u0SGosnh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;H and Buc-ee&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/FxmCqwuh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;H and Buc-ee&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/maps/dallas.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dallas-map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Zack Woodmansee</name><uri>https://github.com/woodmanzee</uri></author><category term="Travel" /><category term="Dallas" /><category term="Texas" /><category term="Wanderlust" /><summary type="html">Because we went into the city last night, we didn’t go back to the heart of Dallas today. Zack had a bunch of work to do so we stayed in the house most of the morning. We have been staying with some friends at their in-laws’ place. The in-laws have a beautiful ranch and were nice enough to let us all crash at their place for the last two nights. I have definitely had the full Texas experience…or the Texas experience that comes to my mind. The ranch has a few cows (longhorns), horses, and two cute dogs. It’s a dream come true for me because I love all of those things! It really is a beautiful place and I can see the appeal of country living. There’s plenty of wide open space to roam and explore. It is also quiet and peaceful, which is nice after navigating through Dallas rush hour traffic yesterday.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kansas to Texas</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Kansas-to-Texas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kansas to Texas" /><published>2017-02-06T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-02-06T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Kansas-to-Texas</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Kansas-to-Texas/">&lt;p&gt;Today was yet another travel day. We took it easy leaving our Wichita hotel room, giving us plenty of time to workout (no more hills thank goodness) and time to get some real work in before getting in the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we were on the road again! The first half was pretty quiet, just more prairie buuut we made it into Oklahoma. Zack says it’s Kansas “with a little spice. There were a few more trees and a few more hills, but not a lot much else!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ahcoGkRl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;OK landscape&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For lunch we stopped at Nic’s Grill in Oklahoma City. It’s this small little spot with very little space, basically a bar and three tables. Also it’s cash only - which thankfully we had some on hand. The menu was simple enough, either a burger + fries or their special of the day + fries and while this seems like a boring menu, their burgers were amazing! They were MASSIVE and the patties were thick and sooo juicy. They offered a few different toppings but my favorite was the grilled onions. They were almost charred, black even, but it added so much flavor to the burger. The fries were also freshly cut - sorta how In-n-Out does it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Gox8lWkh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nic's Grill&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, Nic’s was better. 10/10 would recommend to a friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After lunch we went to check out the state capitol before leaving town. I was surprised that it was nowhere near the heart of the city because, well, I have never seen that before. Most capitol buildings that I have seen (not that I have seen SO many in my lifetime) have been right in downtown or on some hill that is on the edge of the city but overlooks it. Clearly this trip will be very educational for me as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Commentary by Z: the state capitol had a big oil tower in the parking lot. What? Why? Apparently they found oil underneath the capitol building so they drilled a diagonal shaft to get to it… chill guys. It’s the capitol building. Leave it alone and go find oil somewhere else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/b2CpxGph.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;OK State Capitol&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/mB6kAldh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;OK capitol Z/H&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After our extended lunch break, we resumed our drive to Dallas but before we made it to the Texas border we headed off the freeway to Turner Falls. This waterfall is one of the tallest waterfalls in OK (there is another in a state park that matches its height of 77ft - so the internet says). We had to pay to get into the park, but at $8.50 it was well worth it. The river was so blue with natural deep pools where locals and tourists come swim in the summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ojaDR55h.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TurnerFalls river&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An easy path took us right to the falls. It seemed so random in a place that had been flat for so long to suddenly have the gorgeous hills and a waterfall nestled in between it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Svbe38vh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TurnerFallsZ&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/gtXUH3eh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;FallsZH&quot; /&gt;
(We are only a little weird)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The park also has a castle that was built in the 30’s as a summer home. And yes, I said castle. The building sits on the mountainside and is open to the public to explore which we most definitely did!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/AnZyDT3h.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TFcastle&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Oh6FFyRh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TFcastleZH&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/jzb77Dqh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TurnerFallsH&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another great stop in this trip!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Commentary by Z: this “castle” is like every boy scout’s dream… even for a grown up boy scout like myself. It’s like somebody just got bored and decided “hey, there’s tons of rocks around here, I bet I could build myself a sweet little fort up on this hillside” and then before you know it, it becomes this massive project with multiple rooms and 10 fireplaces and secret staircases. There were a few other families/couples there, and from each one it was the man that was way overly excited and was followed around by his polite spouse and kids. Was kind of sad to leave it but I def spent the next 20 minutes in the car thinking about how I could make one of those in my own backyard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We finally made it to Dallas and met up with some friends of ours at Velvet Taco for dinner. This place had their own twist on tacos. They offered a variety of protein: chicken, steak, fish, tofu, etc. but then topped them off with different salsas, dressings, and other yummy things. I got a fish taco and a rotisserie chicken taco. Both were excellent but my favorite was the fish taco. It was great to catch up with old friends and enjoy dinner in the city. After dinner Zack bought a slice of red velvet cake because dessert is always a good way to finish off dinner. The cake was delicious! So moist and dense with lots of frosting, just the way I like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3rd leg of the Journey: ~8 hours. 412 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/maps/dallas.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dallas-map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Zack Woodmansee</name><uri>https://github.com/woodmanzee</uri></author><category term="Travel" /><category term="Kansas" /><category term="Texas" /><category term="Oklahoma" /><category term="Wanderlust" /><summary type="html">Today was yet another travel day. We took it easy leaving our Wichita hotel room, giving us plenty of time to workout (no more hills thank goodness) and time to get some real work in before getting in the car.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Colorado to Kansas</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/colorado-to-kansas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Colorado to Kansas" /><published>2017-02-05T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-02-05T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/colorado-to-kansas</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/colorado-to-kansas/">&lt;p&gt;I kinda dreaded this part of the trip. For the most part we have planned out our trip so that our drive time is no more than 4.5 hours; except for the first two segments of our journey. The first part, Utah to Colorado, wasn’t bad because we had the mountains. I was not looking forward to today’s drive to Kansas because we all know what that means…a whole lot of prairie. Vast open stretches that go on forever. But you know what? I was pleasantly surprised when the drive was pretty fun and actually beautiful (sorry Kansas lovers).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To break up the 7.5 hour drive, we made a few different stops. The first was the “Big Easel”. It’s a huge, 80ft tall art installation to look like an easel holding a Van Gogh Painting in the town of Goodland… so pretty much in the middle of nowhere. It was a great time to stretch our legs, walk around a bit and, of course, take a few pictures!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/cbASDwUl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Zack easel&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was impressed with the size and loved that this city added a little art to attract tourists. We for sure got caught in that trap, and there was another guy near us taking pics too. I’m generally really curious what he was doing because he had a piece of paper with some writing on it that I couldn’t see. He had the paper and easel in view of the camera. Some secret message that I will never know… I hate the feeling of not knowing. Maybe he was proclaiming his love to his girlfriend and Van Gogh was the man to help him out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next break was in Oakley where the Statue of Buffalo Bill stands. The thing was massive! Just look at the picture!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/yt0eJg4l.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;zack on buffalo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The museum was closed being a Sunday and all but they had a stand with information about Buffalo Bill’s famous western show and a little history behind him and the area. To be honest, I had only really heard the name. I didn’t know that much about him, but now I am an expert so feel free to ask any questions regarding his life. Just Kidding. Please don’t do that or I may be embarrassed with the little information I actually retained ha.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our last stop of the trip was one we almost passed up, Zack had found this cool cathedral online but thought it was in Oklahoma. Luckily we saw it in the distance and pulled off the road to take a look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/qnWkGEul.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cathedral&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dubbed “The Cathedral of the Plains”, it turned out to be a 100+ year old cathedral built by German immigrants. I guess their American Dream was moving to Kansas! It makes perfect sense for people who just wanted their own land to farm and to be left alone. The doors were open so we had a chance to sit inside for a moment and enjoy the beauty of the stained glass and other intricate designs adorning the walls, but let’s talk about the stained glass for a moment. There were at least 30+ intricate pieces covering the walls and depicting moments from Christ’s life and various saints caring for His children. I just loved how it was around sunset when we came in so there was soft lighting outside contrasting the dim light inside the church, which made the glass really light up! It’s almost like they were LED powered. It was gorgeous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/PWD67RLl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pulpit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my favorite stop of the day by far. The Church is nestled in a quiet town, which is impressive that these people wanted a beautiful place to worship so they built one. I can only imagine the time and money it must have taken to make the cathedral what it is today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kansas has surprised me. Even in winter, when the grass is dead and the farms are waiting for the growing season, the plains were beautiful. It made me appreciate how vast the US is. There is so much land and amazing things to see. These stops slowed us down a bit while en route to our final destination for the night in Wichita, but it was worth it. We enjoyed the journey so much more when we strayed from the Freeway a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second leg of the journey: Colorado to Kansas. 9 hours, 535 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/maps/kansas.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;kansas&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Zack Woodmansee</name><uri>https://github.com/woodmanzee</uri></author><category term="Colorado" /><category term="Kansas" /><category term="Wanderlust" /><category term="Roadtrip" /><summary type="html">I kinda dreaded this part of the trip. For the most part we have planned out our trip so that our drive time is no more than 4.5 hours; except for the first two segments of our journey. The first part, Utah to Colorado, wasn’t bad because we had the mountains. I was not looking forward to today’s drive to Kansas because we all know what that means…a whole lot of prairie. Vast open stretches that go on forever. But you know what? I was pleasantly surprised when the drive was pretty fun and actually beautiful (sorry Kansas lovers).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Our Day in Denver</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/our-day-in-denver/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our Day in Denver" /><published>2017-02-04T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-02-04T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/our-day-in-denver</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/our-day-in-denver/">&lt;p&gt;We only had a single day to spend in Colorado so we had to make the most of it! With that in mind we started off our day with… a run! Exactly what most people would do right? We gotta stay somewhat in shape with all this inevitable eating out. My aunt and uncle live in a brand new neighborhood on top of this nice big hill. Wonderful for the view of the city, horrible for running. Naturally we ran up it anyways. It was brutal, but we did it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the workout we headed into the city and onto 16th street, a downtown pedestrian strip with lots of food and shopping. We walked along the street with no real destination in mind. There’s something fun about not having an agenda and just wandering in whatever store catches your eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/gx3jEo2l.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;16th street&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/qfKQ7gMl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Zack in the bookstore&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zack found his happy place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After an hour or two we checked out Union Station. It was amazing to see how the city has turned this old train hub into a very classy meet and greet slash hangout area, with leather chairs and nice wooden tables surrounded by little coffee and dessert shops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For lunch, we went to a place called Avanti Food and Beverage just outside the city. When you walk in there’s a few different restaurants inside the building, but they’re all inside individual shipping containers. So it’s kind of like a food truck roundup but indoors and in shipping crates… kind of hard to describe! They had several different options (Schawarma - which I got - sushi, italian, american, etc) and some nice tables and benches in the middle. It had a very modern young-tech-town feel to it, I’d recommend you go if you’re in the area!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today also turned out to be our trial and error day. We planned a few things (the Newman side of us) but not everything (the Woodmansee side of us - or at least the male Woodmansees!). We were left with a few more hours and so it slowed us a down a bit. We would find something we wanted to do but then found out that they were closed. Take a tour of the Pepsi Center? Closed 10min ago. Take a tour of the Hammond Candy Factory? Closed half an hour ago. Take a tour of the Denver Mint? Need a reservation ahead of time. It was really no big deal but we could have saved time driving to no where for a bit. That’s part of the fun though, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After much deliberation and driving around in circles while googling what was still open, we ended up at the house of the “unsinkable” Molly Brown. Naturally it was about to close, but we still saw the gorgeous exterior and went into the carriage-house-turned-gift-shop and the employees were nice enough to tell us a bit of the place’s history before shooing out the door so they could close up. Since everything in Denver was closed just to spite us, we decided to just walk around the State Capitol building grounds before calling it a day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/gkLPOzql.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Molly Brown House&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/VFcJl70l.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;CO Capitol&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was an exciting day and by the end we were ready to go back and hang out with family for the rest of the night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/maps/denver.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Zack Woodmansee</name><uri>https://github.com/woodmanzee</uri></author><category term="Denver" /><category term="Colorado" /><category term="Wanderlust" /><summary type="html">We only had a single day to spend in Colorado so we had to make the most of it! With that in mind we started off our day with… a run! Exactly what most people would do right? We gotta stay somewhat in shape with all this inevitable eating out. My aunt and uncle live in a brand new neighborhood on top of this nice big hill. Wonderful for the view of the city, horrible for running. Naturally we ran up it anyways. It was brutal, but we did it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Utah to Colorado</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/utah-to-colorado/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Utah to Colorado" /><published>2017-02-03T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-02-03T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/utah-to-colorado</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/utah-to-colorado/">&lt;p&gt;The story of us and our year of travel: A few months ago Zack and I decided to do a lot more traveling this year. Zack currently works at GitHub and can work remote; freeing him up to go just about anywhere as long as he has internet and his laptop. I was working for a company, IdealShape, and while I loved it, I could’t leave for weeks at a time…so that left me with one option really. It was a hard decision, but I traded work for travel. Ya I know, rough life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here we are. We are driving across the US. 27ish states. 45 days. The plan is to drive through Colorado, then down to Texas and work our way along the east coast seeing friends, family, and cities that we have always heard about but haven’t seen for ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t sleep much last night. Maybe it was just nervous energy or excitement to get on the road? I ended up paying for that on the drive and was so tired all day. Oh well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First leg of the journey: Utah to Colorado. 8 hours, 506 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/yxjqbQ3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sample Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/WQUhRKa.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sample Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My aunt and uncle were nice enough to let us crash at their place while we check out Denver: my hometown!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/rcRc3aR.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sample Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight on the menu: we found this little greek inspired restaurant called Bada Bing Grill in Arvada. We each got a gyro (finally learned how to say the dang word) and it was the best YEE-row I have ever tasted. To be real for a sec, I don’t even know what kind of meat was in it. Definitely not chicken…or beef. It was sorta like sausage but maybe it was lamb?? I should have asked but because it was so good, I didn’t even care. I also tried their greek salad, which I guess is just a salad? Not sure what part of it was Greek. That was also fantastic!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ended up not even going into Denver tonight, I was so tired from my night of restless sleep that the idea of relaxing and talking to family was far more appealing than running around town. But we’ll make it there tomorrow I promise!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/maps/denver.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Zack Woodmansee</name><uri>https://github.com/woodmanzee</uri></author><category term="travel" /><category term="Utah" /><category term="Colorado" /><category term="Wanderlust" /><category term="Travel" /><summary type="html">The story of us and our year of travel: A few months ago Zack and I decided to do a lot more traveling this year. Zack currently works at GitHub and can work remote; freeing him up to go just about anywhere as long as he has internet and his laptop. I was working for a company, IdealShape, and while I loved it, I could’t leave for weeks at a time…so that left me with one option really. It was a hard decision, but I traded work for travel. Ya I know, rough life.</summary></entry></feed>
